This subtitle is a fan-made translation and
not affiliated with the original content creators.
"Take...the time together"
"To go on..."
"Feel my love"
"Free the time together"
"To go on..."
"Take the time together"
Brother
We can find a solution
to all your problems.
Tell me whatever is on your mind.
I can't remember anything.
Try your maximum!
Have you ever seen a mystery?
What? Tell me!
The stress of not being
able to complete something.
Is there anything like
that haunting you?
Hey. can I ask you something?
Hey…
Can I ask you something?
Why are you working there
under so much stress?
Won't he be there?
That's necessary. Peter.
I need to see him
to prevail over my mind.
Ravi sir had informed me.
This wasn't necessary.
Go on in.
I can't. Prakash.
I just can't.
How many times have we tried?
I'm fed up.
Can you just kill me?
I'm asking seriously!
Can I ask you something serious?
Is there any point
in saying this every single day?
We are undergoing
treatment. aren't we?
It takes time.
You know it. right?
For my sake.
give it a little more time.
Eat quickly and get ready.
Don't we have to go?
Leave me alone
I'll just stay here.
Let's not do that.
If you sit here alone. your mind
will be filled with unnecessary thoughts.
Just come with me to the hospital
and sit in the restroom.
I can keep an eye on you there.
With this breathlessness and pain.
I can't even answer
if anyone asks me anything.
Hey!
Everyone there knows
you're unwell and on voice rest.
So. my dear. eat quickly
and get ready.
"Fire of passion"
"Embers of obsession. you are"
"Now you've drawn so close"
"A flame that consumes
My entire being"
"Oh. pale moonlight.
Upon these crimson lips"
"You are the sweet melody"
"Fire of passion"
"Embers of obsession. you are"
"Now you've drawn so close"
"A flame that consumes
My entire being"
"Oh. pale moonlight.
Upon these crimson lips."
"You are the sweet melody"
"Oh. pale moonlight.
Upon these crimson lips"
"You are the sweet melody"
"Fire of passion"
"Embers of obsession. you are"
Just relax!
No matter what.
we're one at heart. right?
That's enough for us now.
Along with congratulating you
on this international award.
I'd also like to ask a few questions
our audience wants answered.
Son. I've set out breakfast for you.
- Good morning.
- Morning
- Okay.
- She's early today.
With specialist doctors
and modern medical equipment.
'it's a fully equipped
multi-specialty hospital now.'
'What is the magic behind this
rapid growth in such a short time?'
'Hard work and dedication.
not just mine. but my partners' too.'
'This hospital was a dream of ours.'
You're here. yet you've let them
stand there with placards?
Well. sir. since the media got involved
in the issue. I didn't interfere much.
I've already taken care of the media.
Where is our stock?
It's on the third floor.
in the store near General Medicine.
- It needs to be shifted from there.
- Okay. sir.
Do you have
trustworthy people with you?
Yes. it's Santosh.
He is a nurse here.
we can trust him.
He said he'll get it for us tonight.
Sir. what about the CCTV?
I'll handle the CCTV.
- You can go.
- Okay sir.
What's the status of the liver
function test for the patient in 502?
Done. It's normal.
- What about Rosamma's saturation?
- Her saturation is normal. but she's not.
- What do you mean. Santosh?
- I was at the IT station last night.
That old lady kept
ringing the alarm all night.
Santosh wasn't
on night duty yesterday. right?
Well. Fatima has her exam today.
So I took the night shift.
If she stays awake.
it could affect her exam.
- That's so much love. right?
- It's just a help.
I want to say something
for everyone to hear.
I'm the one assigning duty here.
Only those who
can follow that should stay here.
- Understand?
- Yes ma'am.
- Oh. this grandma… Come!
- This old lady…
- What happened. Grandma?
- My dear…
I feel restlessness in my chest.
Look. this alarm
is not for using all the time.
You should only use it
if you feel unbearably sick
or if you are alone
and need help. okay?
Whether she is here or not.
it's all the same.
We took two ECGs yesterday
because she complained of chest pain.
But everything was normal.
She can say that. but what if
something happens to me?
She will only lose a mother-in-law.
but for my son.
he will lose his mother.
Nothing will happen to you. Mom.
You will be fine. okay?
Take rest!
Okay.
You will stay here. right?
I'll be back after my rounds.
or possibly only after OP.
Go ahead and eat
lunch if you're hungry.
No one will disturb you here.
I told the staff to stay out.
even for cleaning.
Did you take a book to read today?
It's in the bag.
I'll be right back.
- Good morning.
Sir. it's Ashokan K S.
53 years of age.
Type two diabetes
since fifteen years and RA.
Present with on-and-off
episodes of fever.
Difficulty in breathing. low levels
of saturation below 90 degree.
- Where are his bystanders?
- They were just here. They've gone out.
He's under observation. right?
Didn't I say the bystanders
should always be here?
Otherwise. you should
assign a nurse here.
Okay.
- Any discomfort right now?
- I'm having trouble breathing. doctor.
He needs to be given nebulization.
I meant right now.
It's fine.
Have you had breakfast?
Yes. I have.
Door closing.
Hey. don't go. don't go.
Door opening.
Hey. Pathu. I sent you
a message yesterday. right?
I saw the blue ticks.
but there was no reply.
Door closing.
- Wasn't it a broadcast message?
- No.
Isn't this the same message
you sent to Reema in Ortho?
Oh. that was just flirting.
But you aren't like that. are you?
Aren't we soul mates?
Let it go. doctor!
Let us live somehow.
Hey. I am serious.
Hey. no matter what.
you have to give me an answer.
Otherwise. I'll jump off
this building. I swear.
I swear on you.
Aby!
Aby. stay there!
Don't default on your daughter's fees.
"Haven't we met somewhere before?"
"So far away until this moment"
"The moment you arrived.
the pages of my life"
"Became a golden script"
"Wasn't it a search. until now?"
"Aren't you close. from now on?"
"Fire feels like a chill.
night blooms into day"
"Each day. like a rose"
"Pain turns to faith.
truth turns to dreams"
"Each day. like a rose"
"Haven't we met somewhere before?"
"So far away until this moment"
"Like the first rain.
An intoxicating drop"
"Falls as a drop of desire"
"The waking breath of my heart"
"And a honeyed melody
Flowing through"
"Did you hear it?"
"Upon these shores. unknowingly"
"Dissolving into every thought"
"Drifting like a ripple"
"Haven't we met somewhere before?"
"So far away until this moment"
"The moment you arrived.
The pages of my life"
"Became a golden script"
"Wasn't it a search. until now?"
"Aren't you close. from now on?"
"Fire feels like a chill.
Night blooms into day"
"Each day. like a rose"
"Pain turns to faith.
Truth turns to dreams"
"Each day. like a rose"
No. Prakash.
Where are you now?
Come here now.
I'm all alone here.
- Please!
- Arundhati. I…
Didn't I tell you?
I'm stuck in traffic. I'll call you back.
This isn't about
caste or religion.
My mother means more to me
than anyone else.
Before we started our relationship.
I told you about my situation. right?
As you are aware.
my mother is a heart patient.
Nothing should happen
to my mother because of me.
Breaking up was a decision
we made together. right?
Just hang up.
I'll call you back.
Right now. you're not
just avoiding one person.
but two people.
Haven't you slept yet?
I didn't feel sleepy.
You can go to bed. Prakash.
You've been busy all day.
I'll sleep later.
Dr. Neena. come fast.
Get the patient on the bed.
- Initiate oxygen support.
- Okay. Ma'am.
One. two. three. four…
- Inject the adrenaline.
- It's not strong enough.
BP is dropping.
Heart rate is slowing.
- He's not responding.
- Give compressions!
I suspect it's cardiac syncope.
What next?
- Inform the cardiologist.
- Okay.
Doctor. three major blocks
are visible in the LCX and LAD.
Given the patient's age.
we are doing a kidney function test.
- The results aren't in yet.
- Okay.
Are the vitals stable?
There is deterioration.
Hello?
Don't worry. Mom.
Nothing will happen to Grandpa.
He has just been taken
into the operation theatre.
Yes.
Check if you can get that ticket.
Okay.
Who is the surgery for?
- It's for my grandpa.
- Oh…
My mother's father.
Doctor. can we know how
Grandpa is doing now?
Of course.
I'll ask and let you know right away.
What happened to Grandpa?
When I got home. Grandpa
was lying there unconscious.
Then. I gave him CPR
as best as I could.
Are you a student?
No. I'm working.
Look. there's no need to worry.
Arundhati ma'am is our new surgeon.
She's worked abroad for a long time.
She only joined here recently.
You can trust her.
- Doctor?
- Now he's okay.
We'll move him to the ICU shortly.
- You can see him then.
- Thank you. Doctor.
- Uh. Madam.
- Yes?
I'm Nikhil.
I'm Prakash sir's junior.
You know. the Pulmonologist.
Also. Doctor
the patient is a relative of mine.
How is he doing now?
There were three blocks.
We've placed a stent.
Thank you. Doctor.
Look. there's nothing to fear.
Also. a stent has been placed.
By the way. I told her
that you're my relative.
That way. your Grandpa
will get much better care.
Okay?
Actually. why don't you
give me your number?
I can call you if
anything is needed.
- 85…
- 85?
- 57.
- 840…
Okay.
Alright.
I'm perfectly fine now.
Don't worry. dear.
Mom is calling. I'll be right back.
No. Grandpa is okay now. Mom.
Yeah.
No. no. there's no problem.
The doctor said there's nothing to fear.
Yeah.
There's a doctor here helping us.
A guy named Nikhil.
They said he'll likely
be moved to a room today.
Sir!
Doctor!
Quick!
- Quickly. call the pulmonologist.
- Okay. ma'am.
This is bad.
- Increase the oxygen level.
- Okay. Doctor.
- Introduce another dose of Epi.
- Sister!
He is stabilized.
Doctor.
- How's Grandpa doing now?
- Daniel is stable for now.
We'll move him to general meds.
I suspect it's COPD.
It's a lung disease.
Let the test results come in first.
Then we can confirm it. Okay?
Hi. hello and welcome.
Our guest today
is the young. charming
Malayali singer Nirmal Sahadev.
- Nirmal bro?
- Yes?
Let's not break the tradition.
We'll start with a few lines
of your song before the interview.
"My dear..."
"Without seeing you."
"I've become longing.
my soul. my every thought."
"You alone..."
"A lifetime that couldn't
embrace you."
- You sing really well!
- Just for fun.
Yes. uncle…
Son. listen to what I'm saying.
Do you have any idea
how much that property is worth
that you don't want to sell
because of your feelings for your dad?
I don't want the money
from selling that property.
Divya had given me her word.
Uncle. that place is in my name.
not my wife's name.
Don't call me
to talk about this again.
Grandma.
It's okay. Yeah!
Nothing to worry.
- Mom. don't be afraid.
- Doctor.
Hydrocort 100 mg.
Start.
Relax. Okay?
Sister. will it take long?
I'm not sure.
The doctor will be here soon.
- Sir. what's the problem?
- It's avascular necrosis.
We need to operate
right away. THR surgery.
Surgery? What for?
- Isn't it just a small back injury?
- Total hip replacement surgery.
If we don't do it now.
he won't even be able to stand.
- Does he drink?
- Only occasionally.
The orthopaedic surgeon is on his way.
Madam. you need to sign
this consent form.
My uncle is the CEO of this hospital.
I can't sign anything
until he gets here.
The doctor decides
on surgery. not the CEO.
If you care about your
husband's health. please sign.
- NIKHIL: IS GRANPA OKAY?
- TIJI: YES. HE IS OKAY.
NIKHIL: I HAD
SOMETHING TO TELL YOU.
TIJI: WHAT IS IT?
NIKHIL: IT NEEDS
TO BE TOLD DIRECTLY.
TIJI: REALLY!
Hello?
Hello. Tiji?
- Yes. Doctor?
- Come outside for a second.
Up to the terrace.
Grandpa's sedated.
He's asleep.
He's asleep. so he doesn't
need your care right now.
But I need you.
Come to the terrace.
Okay.
What is it?
Did seeing me
actually scare you?
- Huh?
- No.
Why do you get nervous
every time you see me?
Huh?
I should go.
Grandpa is all alone.
Hey. Tiji.
Wait. Tiji!
Hold on a second!
Just let me talk.
No! It's not like that! Tiji!
Hey!
Oh. no!
- Abhirami!
- Huh?
Wait. just listen to me!
Let me explain!
Hey!
- Sister!
- Yes?
Sister. call the doctor!
Grandpa's in bad shape.
Hello?
I'm on my way.
Not asleep yet?
I couldn't sleep.
- Even after the medicine?
- No. not even then.
The patient in 503 is critical.
- I'll go take a look.
- Al right.
No chest rise.
The lungs aren't inflating.
- How is he?
- Not this one.
- Acute respiratory collapse.
- It's…
The lungs aren't
responding properly.
Go and charge the AED. hurry!
Here.
Time of death: 2:47.
Doctor…
I'm sorry.
Don't beat yourself up.
We did everything we could.
Still…
We don't need to stay here.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Hey. what's wrong?
A patient died today.
What?
Take it easy.
Just go home and try
to get some rest.
I get such a negative
vibe from him.
From whom?
Who else?
Prakash.
Don't think like that.
We can't go through life only
dealing with people we like.
Can we?
Are you okay?
You're fine?
It's not just the medicine
making me feel better.
Then what is it?
You have some kind of magic.
They call it a "healing touch.”
don't they?
Not really.
You only feel that way because
your pain faded so quickly.
No.
You are the "Angel of Life!"
Regretting calling
me "Angel of Life" yet?
Sometimes death is a relief. Prakash.
No surgical complications.
But there's an infection.
Especially in the lungs.
That's why he was shifted.
It's early-stage pneumonia.
Also. some variations in the ECG.
The doctors will come here. Okay?
Dear…
The drop eye test doesn't
show anything to worry about.
Caused by surgical stress.
We'll recheck the ECG
and Echo in a couple of days.
I'm not letting you go until
you're well and sing a few songs.
Okay?
Okay. then.
- How are you now?
- It's a bit hard to breathe.
- Hasn't your dad arrived yet?
- I don't know.
How are you. Nirmal?
- It's fine.
- You'll have everything you need here.
Okay?
Haven't you and
your dad made up yet?
It's not me who's holding a grudge.
She only listens to her mom.
My hands are tied.
Dear…
You should reconsider what I said.
We'll both benefit from this.
Anyway. you get some rest.
Don't hesitate to call
if you need anything.
Okay?
Do you even care
about me at all?
If you did. you would
have given that land to Uncle.
After all. he's just
my uncle. right?
I'm the only one
who has commitments.
Go on. You don't need to sit here.
I just need to sleep peacefully.
Either you leave. or I'm leaving.
It's not just your uncle
who owns a hospital in this town.
Get out! Just get lost!
Fine. just keep lying there then.
'Abhi. nothing happened
as you are thinking'
'It's all your suspected doubts'
'Is there any other girl
in my life other than you?'
'Abhi. could you come up
to the top floor? I'm right here.'
'Give me a chance
to make it up to you.'
'Please.'
I knew you'd come.
Dear… Dear wake up.
What is it. Mom?
After all. isn't it your
husband who's lying there?
Can't you go
and see him once in a while?
He's the one who
told me to get out of there.
Do whatever you want.
What happened?
Hello.
Yeah. Coming.
- I'll be right back. You go to sleep.
- Okay.
Sir. severe metabolic acidosis.
pH is 6.9 and dropping.
Heart rate is erratic.
We should go on ECG.
Give the shock!
Charge AED to 200 Joules!
Fast!
Pupils are fixed and dilated.
Time of death. 2:47.
I'm unable to accept Nirmal's death.
My head is starting to throb.
Shall we have a tea?
Ragitha! Ragitha!
Ragitha!
Hello.
What a deep sleep!
Aren't you going to the hospital today?
What's the matter. Doctor?
Sir
Maybe this is just my intuition.
But I can't just dismiss it.
Someone here is murdering
my patients on purpose.
Sir. I need you to
spearhead an investigation
See. Doctor
the whole point of patients
coming here is to stay alive.
If news of murders spreads.
would anyone dare
come to this hospital?
Better I just shut the place down.
A few of your patients died.
That's a fact.
But you cannot be held
responsible for that.
No matter how sincerely doctors try.
patients don't always survive.
Those are things beyond our control.
These deaths have put you
under immense stress.
You must get
some relief from that stress.
Go see our psychiatrist for a bit.
Get yourself
some antidepressants.
It'll help calm you down.
Anyway. I'm already under pressure.
Monitor the saturation
of the patient in 452 every hour.
- Okay. Ma'am. Good night.
- Good night.
Good night. Sir.
[Indistinct chatters]
What is it. Doctor?
Why aren't you
answering my calls?
Where have you been
all this time?
Do you know how much
I struggled to find this place?
You already know
about my family.
Don't you know I chose
this profession to please my mother?
You were carrying then--
I didn't know you were pregnant.
Even you found out late. right?
I didn't do this intentionally.
I was thinking about my family.
the preferences
of my mother and father.
It's only because of
that I left you.
Please forgive me.
Don't destroy yourself
out of spite for me.
Come. let's go
to a de-addiction center.
Please come with me.
What are you
thinking about so deeply?
This isn't just my suspicion.
Arundhati came to the hospital…
to take revenge on me.
Did you know?
She's still using drugs.
I even found codeine
in her room today.
Isn't that a painkiller?
So what?
She knows exactly how to use
that medicine as a drug.
She's still psychic.
I'm sure of it.
She's the one killing my patients.
Did you eat?
It's okay.
It's better than yesterday.
I was on night duty yesterday.
that's why I couldn't call.
I'll try asking.
One second.
Oxygen level is okay.
- Hydrostat 200 mg.
- Okay. sir.
Pulse is weak.
- Check rhythm.
- It's stable. sir.
Sister. here.
It's okay.
Don't scare.
- Check the vitals. okay?
- Okay. sir.
You should be here.
Call me if there's an emergency.
Sister…
Hey. it's not like that.
I didn't ignore you.
Don't even get me started.
A patient suddenly became critical.
Oh no! Don't hang up.
Don't hang up. listen to me.
It's because she's used
to pressing the nursing alarm
we managed to save her now.
If I had been a little late
it would've been the same situation
as Daniel and Nirmal.
Rosamma's saturation was normal.
When the blood
oxygen level is normal.
it is unusual for a respiratory attack
to be fatal like this.
What are you getting at. Prakash?
Has someone injected
any fatal medicine
into Rosamma's body?
If that is the case. should we
not check the blood immediately?
Look. as a government toxicologist.
I am not supposed to do this.
I am only getting
involved for you.
As you said. a specific
compound is present in it.
- What is it?
- Look…
you only just gave me
the blood samples. right?
I need to trace it.
How much more time
will you need. Girish?
- About two weeks.
- Okay.
Can I ask you something else?
Why are you doing this all alone?
Why don't you tell
the hospital management
and start a police investigation?
I tried all that. Girish.
It is no use.
Anyway. try to speed this up
as much as possible.
We will see after
the results are out.
All right.
Sir. remember you asked
if anyone was visiting
your patients without reason?
- Yeah.
- Yes. sir.
We did not have any such suspicion
when you asked then.
- But…
- Arundhati madam.
Your patients are
her patients too. right?
Arundhati madam visits the patients
even when there are no rounds.
- Is that not right?
- Yes. sir.
- I have seen that too.
- Yeah.
All right. do not mention this
to anyone else for now.
Hello.
Connect me to Cardiac
Surgeon Arundhati.
- Hello?
- Arundhati. it is Prakash.
I have patients here.
What is it?
I need to see you in person.
Not here.
Somewhere outside is fine.
I have nothing to discuss with you.
Arundhati.
I am not trying to dig up our past.
This does not just concern us.
We must meet.
Otherwise. you will have to face
the consequences alone.
Hi. Prakash. I'm Peter.
- I am Arundhati's partner.
- I need to speak to Arundhati alone.
Okay.
You two talk.
I will be over there.
- Okay.
- Sit down.
Whatever it is. be quick.
I have work to do.
Are you still using drugs?
Is this why you gave
such a big build-up?
That is my personal matter.
- You do not need to know.
- I need to know.
- I must know.
- Why?
Someone at our hospital…
is deliberately injecting
my patients with a medicine.
And it leads to their death.
I suspect it is you.
Hello.
Someone is murdering patients
in your General Medicine department
with lethal injections.
Hello? Hello?
- Hello?
- Someone is murdering patients…
- Hello. Medical City Hospital.
- Hello?
Hello?
You don't need to worry so much
about an anonymous phone call.
It might just be a prank call.
But if the media finds out.
it will affect our reputation.
The staff are all
in a panic. sir.
- You must do something. Sir.
- Let me investigate this anyway.
If needed. I will have the police
conduct an investigation.
- You may leave for now.
- All right. sir.
- Okay. sir.
- Thank you.
So Vivek. your leave
is over. isn't it?
It has. sir.
I need to extend it a little more.
I will grant it. but
on one condition.
I need you to investigate a case
that I have a personal interest in.
It can be unofficial for now.
If you find any substance to it.
we can make it official.
Please excuse me from this. sir.
- I'm not in a good mood.
- What happened to you?
Sir. remember a charge sheet
for a case I submitted last year?
- Which one? The POCSO case?
- Yes.
The court acquitted
him last week.
They cited a lack of evidence.
I just cannot accept that.
Look. you are a police officer.
Your job is to catch criminals
and bring them before the law.
The court decides the rest.
Even so…
I should have found
more scientific evidence.
You have always been like this.
You let these cases
get into your head
and then stress
yourself out unnecessarily.
Just look into
what I am telling you.
All right.
What should I investigate?
Medical City Hospital.
Their CEO. Gopinath.
is a close friend of mine.
I know.
Father Joshua who was my
guardian at the orphanage
died there.
Today. the hospital received
an anonymous call.
They claimed someone is trying to kill
the General Medicine patients.
Go and find out
if there is any truth to it.
And go alone.
The media
must not get a whiff of this.
The investigation should not affect
the hospital's goodwill.
I want full details
when you return from leave.
Sir…
Wait. how is this a leave then?
If you stay single like this.
you might have to work
during leave too.
I am Vivek Tharakan.
I have investigated
thirty three cases so far.
I managed to bring
all 33 culprits before the law.
Three of them were acquitted
due to lack of evidence.
This is the case right in front of me.
A hospital.
Two abnormal deaths.
A place where people
come seeking life.
Whoever is sentencing them to death
must not remain hidden in the dark.
I must find them.
Darkness has ruled long enough.
Now it's time for justice.
- Excuse me?
- Yes. Sir.
Dr. Prakash?
He's on his rounds now.
OP time is 11:30.
- Okay. thanks.
- Thank you.
Sir.
The CCTV often has technical issues.
Only the visuals from
that day are missing.
I have reported it to the CEO.
CI Vivek.
Oh…
- SP Shiyaz sent you. right?
- Yes.
The CCTV footage
for several days is missing.
The operator told me
to ask you about it.
Are there any illegal activities
happening here?
No.
Nothing like that.
And as for the CCTV. you know
these are just
technical issues. right?
I will believe that for now.
I need to speak with the staff.
I will make the arrangements.
Okay. see you soon.
Put me to SP Shiyaz.
Why did you suspect this. Doctor?
I felt suspicious about the deaths
of Daniel and Nirmal.
A sudden respiratory attack
was the cause of death for both.
But I had stabilized them
just hours before they died.
I could not find any specific reason
for them to die so suddenly.
Then…
Then?
There was another patient.
Rosamma. who had similar symptoms.
I sent her blood for a checkup.
My friend. a toxicologist. tested it.
It appears a medicine was likely
injected into her blood.
- Did you identify the medicine?
- Nope.
I am actually waiting for the result.
- Inform me as soon as you get it.
- Sure.
Do you suspect anyone?
Huh?
I do.
What nonsense are you saying?
There is no abnormality in the deaths
of Daniel and Nirmal.
- I can say that with certainty.
- That may be true.
But when the management
has a doubt.
the police cannot
just sit idle.
According to my investigation.
many in the hospital suspect you.
Me?
I do not believe that.
- Is this a standard police tactic?
- Do not get emotional.
A doctor has given
a clear statement against you.
Were you not a drug addict before?
I know who said it.
He is a madman.
Did you come to see me
based on what a madman said?
No one would make such
an accusation without a reason.
Mr. Vivek. you must believe me.
I have never done anything
against my medical ethics.
The police cannot immediately judge
if you are lying or not.
There are procedures for that.
What are your procedures?
Usually. a lie detection test
clears things up quickly.
Okay.
Let's do that.
Can I get past your
accusations if I do that?
I am fine with it. I am ready.
Okay. Cool. Doctor.
I was just saying.
It is not necessary for now.
I had a friend
look into all the hospitals
where Arundhati worked before.
That's how I reached you. Nikhitha.
Arundhati and I were together
at Vasanthi Hospital in Hyderabad.
You will keep your promise. right?
Hey. never.
I know how confidential this is.
So. I won't be telling her
this under any circumstances.
Anyway. her nature
is a bit different.
She holds a grudge
even over small things.
But I was very close to her.
Did you feel anything strange
about her behavior back then?
Uh. nothing like that…
I have been thinking about it
since you called yesterday.
But I cannot recall
anything specific.
Think again.
This is a matter
that affects many patients.
I do not know if what I am about
to say will be helpful.
When we were working together.
a patient was in critical condition.
His vitals were unstable.
He was on the verge of death.
He suffered a lot.
Even for us watching.
his suffering was unbearable.
We struggled
a lot to resuscitate him.
But at that moment.
Arundhati said something.
She asked. "Why not euthanize him
instead of making
him suffer even more?"
I asked her what she meant.
She just brushed it off.
Later. when another patient
was critical. she repeated it.
- Did I keep you waiting long?
- No.
Even though you're such a qualified
doctor. why a place like this?
I got tired of working
for money and those who make it.
That is why I chose
a hospital like this.
It has been my wish
since my medical school days.
I wanted to do something
for the people here.
"Where the art of medicine is loved
there is also love of humanity."
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
- Our subject is Arundhati. right?
- Yeah.
When you called.
I went back to old memories.
When we lived together.
Arundhati had a pet dog. Fadey.
It was in a state of total agony
because of Canine Distemper.
The veterinarian said
it could be saved with some care.
But she could not
bear to see it suffer.
She forced the vet
to perform mercy killing.
I could not accept it then.
I wanted to care for it
for a few more days.
No need to be anxious.
I can only investigate
this more effectively
if the case moves
forward officially.
I know. Sir.
I need to find the truth as well.
Yes. why did you call me. Sir?
You don't understand
why we called you. do you?
- You should mind your own business.
- And if I don't?
Hey…
Some young men
are like that. Joseph.
They don't want to work hard.
But they want to get rich quick.
They find their own
shortcuts for it.
They find some billionaire's daughter
and make her fall in love.
Sir. if you are referring to
my relationship with Abhirami.
it isn't for your money or status.
Then why the hell are you
following my daughter?
I will finish you off in a way
even a postmortem can't trace!
And then?
Before you kill me.
I'll tell everyone the truth
about the dealings you and he
have been carrying out
in this hospital.
The expired vaccines.
the Z-Category drugs
and the expired medicines.
I have full details of all
the other medicines you distribute.
If the media finds out…
Actually. I was planning
to come and see you.
That's when you called me here.
That worked out well.
I'll offer you a deal.
I want 20% of the total profit
from all the illegal business
you run in this hospital.
You'd have to give it to me
in the future anyway. wouldn't you?
Don't worry about
the money leaving the family.
Just consider it as something
given to your daughter.
Is that okay. Joseph?
Since the deal is on.
may I leave now?
Sir.
Who gave you permission
to rush into this polygraph test?
Did you have enough
evidence to justify this?
Isn't this done to find evidence. sir?
Besides. if the accused consents
to a lie detection test
then what is the problem?
I'll call you after this is over.
You are being
a bit over-ambitious. Vivek.
What you are doing
is wrong. Officer.
Arundhati isn't fit for this test.
physically or mentally.
And don't forget
that I am a media person.
It won't take me long
to turn this into a news story.
Arundhati Balan is the cardiac surgeon
of Medical City Hospital.
Yes.
Arundhati has a grudge
against Dr. Prakash.
No.
Arundhati wants
to destroy his reputation.
No!
Whatever you say.
I won't issue a warrant
for Arundhati's arrest.
You know the consequences
of arresting a doctor
without scientific evidence.
I'll have to answer
to the Medical Council.
First. stop this habit of arresting
suspects without solid proof.
I'll return with scientific evidence.
Don't give me excuses then. sir.
- Can you--
- Give it here!
- Listen to what I am saying.
- Step aside!
Are you trying to kill me?
Are you?
- Stop.
- Who are you?!
Who are you?
Give that to me.
Isn't this codeine?
- Give it to me!
- Why did Renuka give it to you?
Who are you to ask all that?
You better start talking.
or I'm calling the police.
- Step aside.
- Let go!
Hey!
He is my son. Doctor.
Saneesh.
I spent money I didn't even have
just to send him to Bangalore to study.
But he returned as a drug addict.
He didn't even complete his studies.
I tried advising him so much.
I took him to de-addiction centers.
But nothing changed.
If he doesn't get a fix
he becomes violent with me.
He is my son. sir.
How can I abandon him?
I gave in to his demands.
Now. I take whatever medicines
he asks for from here.
Madhavi helped me with this.
She'd hide the medicine and then
give it to me right before leaving.
One day. Dr. Arundhati
caught Madhavi with the medicine.
I fell at the doctor's feet
and begged her not to report it.
But we never really trusted her.
Is that why you spoke
against Arundhati?
Doctor. I beg of you.
If I lose this job. I'll have no choice
but to end my life.
I did it out of desperation.
- It won't happen again. Doctor.
- That's enough.
Don't say another word.
Get lost!
Doctor. please…
The compound found
in the blood samples you gave me
is pancuronium bromide.
Medical professionals call it Pavulon.
We use pancuronium bromide
during surgeries for anesthesia.
- Yeah.
- A skeletal muscle relaxant.
It is also used for intubation.
An increased heart rate
and respiratory depression
are its adverse effects.
But it isn't preferred for use
in ICU or ventilated patients.
We don't use it
for long-term patients.
If we look at it historically.
in Europe. it was a drug used
for euthanasia or mercy killing.
In the US. it is also used
for the death penalty.
Is this a medicine
that is easily available to the public?
It is easily available to doctors.
Not just doctors.
but also to the OT staff and nurses.
There was a case
where a male nurse. Efren Saldivar.
killed 200 people.
He used this same pancuronium
bromide to kill 50 of them.
If we find traces
of this medicine in her bag.
we can take her into custody.
I didn't feel anything
suspicious that night.
Actually. Grandpa
was quite stable in the evening.
Then there was that
junior doctor. Nikhil.
He came to see me at that time.
Why?
To ask about Grandpa's condition.
He was acting
a bit too friendly that day.
- Gopi Uncle is our relative.
- Who?
Gopinath. the hospital CEO.
He had an eye on
Nirmal's ancestral property.
I was fast asleep
at that time. Sir.
Sir. I killed the patient
by injecting the medicine.
But I can't tolerate the guilt.
I am going to
commit suicide
Yes. sir?
I need the details of death cases
from the last three years.
Specifically those who
died of respiratory attacks
like Daniel and Nirmal.
Yes. sir but that will
take some time.
Call me once the files are ready.
Good morning. Sir.
This is our medicine sample.
Please consider our request. Sir.
I'll see.
- Manoj. call me later.
- I will. Sir.
Thank you.
- Hello.
- Hey!
The medicine sample
you gave me to test
is indeed pancuronium bromide.
The same medicine
that caused your patients' deaths.
Haven't you slept yet?
There is a patient
is little series.
I will be right back
You go to sleep.
Sometimes. isn't death
a mercy. Prakash?
I found a medicine
in the restroom today.
The same medicine
that killed my patients.
No one enters that
room except us.
I don't even let them clean
unless I am there.
How did it get there then?
What are you trying
to say. Prakash?
Humans have a specific nature.
Even when a crime happens
right under their noses.
they still look
for suspects elsewhere.
They never suspect
those closest to them.
We've grown far
too close for this.
Why did you kill my patients?!
Why?!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I am at a point
where I even doubt myself now.
Please forgive me.
Abhi.
Why did you do this?
It wasn't me.
Joseph pushed me.
Your father told him to.
Are you sure you took the pill?
Then there is nothing to fear.
Why did Daddy do this to you?
For loving you.
And to stop me…
from revealing his secrets.
- Abhi…
- Yes?
I need to…
see Vivek sir.
Please?
Is that you. son?
Come in.
You didn't say you were coming.
I need to take a document
from Ragi's room.
Ragitha Prakash.
- She was Dr. Prakash's wife.
- Huh?!
She died at home.
but her death was confirmed here.
Sir. Nikhil has
regained consciousness.
He said he wants
to speak with you.
Sir. I have something
else to tell you.
On the night
Rosamma became critical.
while I was talking on the phone
I felt like our Dr. Prakash
was talking to himself.
At that time. I felt like
something was wrong with him.
"Shadows follow clouds"
"Carving trenches cold and shallow"
"Every step confined"
"Through a pass so tight and narrow"
"Still the dose remains"
"Like a ghost I cannot borrow"
"Behind every dose"
"There stands a boss"
"Shadows"
"follow clouds"
"Every step confined"
"Still the dose remains"
"Behind every dose"
"There stands a boss"
No Ragitha. I'm just...
I need to know who did this.
I just can't believe you.
Didn't all this happen
while you were there?
Why are you being so quiet?
My brain is fried.
Who could have done this?
Ragitha. say something.
Please! Please talk to me!
Vivek Sir…
How did you find this house?
They say. "Seek and you shall find".
Are you heading out?
No. I just got back.
Do you live here alone?
No.
My wife's here.
Ragitha.
Ragitha Prakash.
Doctor Prakash…
when we lose someone we love.
it's normal to feel their presence.
But if you feel that even after a year.
that needs treatment.
It's been a year since
your wife died.
You have to come
with me right now.
I don't mean to
hurt you. Prakash.
But now. I suspect you too.
You're trying to frame
me. aren't you?
She's in on it too. isn't she?
Arundhati.
Get out of here. sir.
Please.
Get out.
- Get out.
- Don't be so emotional. Doctor.
Don't make me resort to force.
Come.
"Shadows follow clouds"
Prakash…
Prakash. what the man!
Hey!
The only person who truly got me.
It was Ragitha.
Our life was heaven.
"Fire of passion"
"Embers of obsession. you are"
"Now you've drawn so close"
"A flame that consumes
My entire being"
"Oh. pale moonlight.
Upon these crimson lips"
"You are the sweet melody"
"Oh. pale moonlight.
Upon these crimson lips"
"You are the sweet melody"
"Fire of passion"
"Embers of obsession. you are"
I often feel that God doesn't like it
when humans are too happy.
Lung cancer began to
take its toll on Ragitha.
None of the treatments worked.
It's the final stage.
"Fire of passion"
She was too frail
to bear the pain and distress.
She started to crave death.
"A flame that consumes
My entire being"
"Oh. pale moonlight.
Upon these crimson lips"
"You are the sweet melody"
I don't know.
If a soul really exists…
if there is such a thing…
if I kill myself…
it may be destroyed.
But if you perform
a mercy killing on me…
it won't be like that.
It is more like a doctor's duty…
in which he saves the patients. right?
In this life…
this is the only gift
you can grant me. Prakash.
Please allow that.
A blessing death.
Please!
But if you perform
a mercy killing on me…
In this life…this is the only gift
you can grant me. Prakash.
Please allow that.
A blessing death.
'DOSE
SECOND OPINION'
Kill me without
hurting me. Prakash.
Later in every suffering patient.
I saw Ragitha.
I found a way to decide
death at any time.
Sometimes. even death is a mercy.
Prakash…
you have two personalities
within you.
One is the savior.
And the other is an avenger.
I now see both of them
merging into one.
"Shadows follow clouds"
The one who
tried to kill the patients.
and the one who
tried to save them…
it was him all along.
I knew then
that he was unstoppable.
Then the relentless rain…
on the school veranda…
I…
Cool.
He spent a long time in a coma.
His identity remains unknown to us.
From what I've gathered
through my investigation.
he used to be a police officer.
His condition is the result
of a post-accident neuro problem.
Fantasy-Prone Personality.
A fantasy world created
by his mind.
In that world. he might see
the people from this hospital.
He turns them into characters
and creates an
investigative story of his own.
I feel that. at some
point in his life.
the stress from an unfinished case
could be the reason for all this.
Either way.
what he's saying isn't real.
Sir. then I have a doubt.
Could a fantasy world
be this precise?
It's not just my doubt. Sir.
I think these are
real events from his past.
Then you teach the class. Doyle!
He has severe breathing problems.
Transfer him to General Medicine.
Okay.
"Shadows follow clouds"
"Carving trenches cold and shallow"
"Every step confined"
"Through a pass so tight and narrow"
"Still the dose remains"
"Like a ghost I cannot borrow"
"Shadows follow clouds"
"Still the dose remains"
"Take...the time together"
"To go on..."
"Feel my love"
"Take the time together"
"To go on..."
"Free the time together"